MY MAMA LOVES ME
I LOVE MY MOM
SEE, I'M A GOOD BOY
I DO NO CRIME
I BRING YOU NO SHAME CUZ THIS IS WHO I AM
AND YEAH YOU RAISED ME
TO BE WHAT I'VE BECOME
MY MAMA LOVES ME BECAUSE I LOVE MY MOM
"I LOVE MY MOM"
SEE, I'M A GOOD BOY MAMA, I DO NO CRIME
"I DO NO CRIME"
I BRING YOU NO SHAME CUZ THIS IS WHO I AM
"THIS IS WHO I AM"
AND YEAH YOU RAISED ME TO BE WHAT I'VE BECOME
لو كان قدامي ظلم
I'LL TRY TO FIGHT IT
EVEN IF MY HANDS ARE TIED MY HEART WILL SHOW DENIAL
لو كان قدامي
PEACE
DO MY BEST TO KEEP IT
سيبلك قصه حلوه
ON THIS EARTH BEFORE YOU LEAVE IT
لما يجي يومي
لا لا , لا لا مابا
مابا , مابا أتمنى إني أرجع للبدايه
مابا اندم عشان في كتابي في أسوأ حكايه
لا تقول دنيا سخيفه , هيا بداية النهايه
مابا , مابا صاحبي يقول طعنته في يوم وليله
كل لقمه وسر كانوا بيننا مالهم قيمه
وإن وصلتنا طعنه نقول "الله يهديه ويهدينا"
يطعنوا ونصدمهم بالنظافه الي فينا
NOW THAT'S WHY MY MAMA LOVES ME
BECAUSE I LOVE MY MOM
"I LOVE MY MOM"
SEE, I'M A GOOD BOY MAMA, I DO NO CRIME
"I DO NO CRIME"
I BRING YOU NO SHAME CUZ THIS IS WHO I AM
"THIS IS WHO I AM"
AND YEAH YOU RAISED ME TO BE WHAT I'VE BECOME
"BABY", SORRY IF I HURT YOU
بس ما شفت مستقبل لينا
THAT'S WHY I CHOSE TO LEAVE WHEN FEELINGS
HAVE COME BETWEEN US
I LOVE MYSELF TO DEATH. WON'T GIVE MYSELF
لأي بنت لذينه
مين فينا معصوم ؟
قولوا ربي توب علينا SO
BABY GIRL BELIEVE ME
الحرام ما عاد يغريني
GOT HURT AND HURT ENOUGH. A BROKEN HEART
ما حيفيدني
مابا اخذ منك , ما بعطيك SO لا تعطيني
GIRLS I KNOW YOU'RE SMART SO
بدون الخاتم
DON'T BELIEVE HIM, NAH
DON'T EVEN BELIEVE ME
قريني ما حيسيبني
بس طول مافيني روح حفضل واقف
HE WON'T DEFEAT ME
I WILL NEVER SAY I'M PERFECT
IN ME, THERE'S DARKNESS LURKING
AND IT WILL NEVER BE OUT IN THE OPEN
I'LL KEEP STRIVING. GOD PLEASE GUIDE ME THROUGH THIS WAY
MY MAMA LOVES ME BECAUSE I LOVE MY MOM
خلاص خمن باقي الكلمات